{"data":[{"question":"I am writing to tell you how much I had enjoyed the few hours I spent with you and your family yesterday evening.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"am writing","b":"how much","c":"had enjoyed","d":"spent","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Had enjoyed-> enjoyed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I have been in England for the beginning of October and this was my first invitation to dinner with an English family.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have been","b":"for","c":"was","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- For-> since","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I found the conversational most interesting and was glad to practise my English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"found","b":"conversational","c":"interesting","d":"glad","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Conversational-> conversation","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I would also like congratulating you on your excellent cooking.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"also","b":"congratulating","c":"on","d":"cooking","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Congratulating->to congratulate","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I was very gratefully for all the helpful information you gave me about the courses in English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"gratefully","c":"information","d":"about","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Greatfully-> greatful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I hope to find a suitable school within the next few day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to find","b":"suitable","c":"within","d":"day","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Day-> days","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The English courses will not be too hard to me to study.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"courses","b":"will not","c":"too","d":"to","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- To-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Would please you give my best wishes to your husband and children?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"please","b":"give","c":"best","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Please-> would you please","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you again with an extremely pleasant evening.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Thank","b":"with","c":"extremely","d":"pleasant","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- With-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"A house in that district will cost you at less 200,000.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"district","c":"will cost","d":"at less","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Less-> least","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}